Sepehr **Razmyar**

Tehran, Iran

🛘 +989215207826 | 💌 sepehrjamshid@hotmail.com | 🌴 null3rror.github.io/Portfolio/ | 🖸 Null3rror | 🛅 Sepehr-Razmyar | 😘 live:sepehrjamshid

Summary_

Unity programmer. BS in Computer Engineering in progress. Skilled in Unity & C#. Strong knowledge on design patterns, principles & best practices. I'm interested in Game AI, therefore I took some graduate Reinforcement Learning courses. For more projects please visit my itch.io

Skills_

Programming C#, Python, C++, C, Bash scripting, Writing clean, reuseable & readable code

Parallel Programming Compute Shaders, CUDA, OpenMP, Intel SIMD

Artificial Intelligence Unity ML Agents, Reinforcement Learning, Neural Networks, Deep Learning

Networking REST API, Photon, Encryption, Network protocols, Wireshark

Testing Unit testing, Mocking **Tools** Git, Version control

Mathematics University level math, 3D mathematics **Problem Solving** Algorithms, Data structures, Bit masking

Microcontrollers Experience with embedded systems design using the Arduino programming environment

Work Experience _____

Dionic Software Munich, Germany (Remote)

GAME PROGRAMMER ON Founders' Fortune, FULL-TIME

May. 2022 - Present

- Responsible for maintaining and implementing new gameplay features for Founders' Fortune

Pars Cog, University of Tehran

Tehran, Iran

LEAD PROGRAMMER, UNITY GAME DEVELOPER

Jul. 2021 - Feb. 2022

- · Performed as Software Architect & Unity Developer developing & architecting game components
- Developed 2D & 3D Corsi Block for visual/auditory memory improvement of children & elders
- Led a junior programmer to develop a Dementia assessment game

Amytis Games

UNITY GAME DEVELOPER INTERN

Jul. 2019 - Sep. 2019

- Programmed a configurable 2D enemy AI with animations
- · Improved their path system from waypoint based to Bezier spline by implementing an editor tool which you can edit the spline in the scene
- · Programmed a matchmaking system using Photon Networking
- · Programmed camera control for a mobile game

Projects ____

Super Crash UFOs (72h Game Jam) Remote USA, England, Iran S.P.H.E.R.E

Tehran, Iran

LEAD PROGRAMMER

• Programmed UFO's movement, abduction, dropping...

- Designed UFO's power up base architecture
- Programmed power ups such as Black Hole, Shield &, Boost
- Implemented local multiplayer logic using Unity's New Input System
- Used math to create smooth abduction animation
- Responsible for the Portal (drop zone) & its shader & particles

Oct. 2021 Solo Unity Developer

Jun. 2021

- · Based on Trials Evolution's mini game, this game was developed to represent our Xbox Remote Controller
- Programmed ball's movement & behavior
- Programmed custom occlusion to segment levels into zones for opti-
- Programmed dynamic obstacles & steams

SEPEHR RAZMYAR · RÉSUMÉ MAY 31, 2022

Prince of Persia's rewind mechanic 🗹 | 🛗

A Man Looking for His Organs 🗹

SOLO UNITY DEVELOPER

with theme of "Repair"

Tehran, Iran

Feb. 2020

SOLO UNITY DEVELOPER

Jul. 2019

- A 3rd person game which you can rewind time like Prince of Persia
- Programmed rewinding time mechanic & visuals effects
- · Programmed character movement
- · Used Blend Trees for movement animations

Tank Trouble using PyGame Tehran, Iran

· The player has to fight enemies, gather his organs & shoot his way out

· Programmed player & AI behavior

Used Object Pooling for bullets to optimze the game

Jan. 2018

Qazvin, Iran

SOLO PROGRAMMER & ARTIST • 2D game developed using PyGame(Python)

- Supports local multiplayer & supports Xbox & PS4 controllers
- Implemented horde (survival) mode with waypoint based Als
- Implemented shotgun, big ball & shield power up

Pacman using A* algorithm 🗹 | 🛗 SOLO UNITY DEVELOPER

Jul. 2019

• Pacman game were each ghost has different strategy

• Programmed ghosts to use A* for pathfinding

Xbox Remote Controller A 🔾

Tehran, Iran

Nerf Gun as a VR Gun Contoller

Tehran, Iran

SERVER SIDE & ANDROID PROGRAMMER

Jun. 2021

Jul. 2021

- Your Android device can act as an Xbox controller
- Support multiplayer, up to 4 players, useful for when you're short on controllers
- Support multiple layouts for different games, e.g., gyroscope layout for driving games
- Supports Unity games & every game that supports Xbox controller
- SOLO PROGRAMMER

• Turned a Nerf gun to a gun controller for PC, Xbox, PS4 games which acts as a mouse & keyboard using Arduino

• 2D platformer game developed in 48 hours for Global Game Jam 2020,

- Pull the trigger in real life, it'll shoot in game
- Reload in real life, it'll reload in game
- Use the buttons & thumb stick to walk, jump, interact etc.
- · Works on every FPS game
- Melee in real life, it'll melee in game, check the video for more details

Education

University of Tehran Tehran, Iran

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Sep. 2017 - Jun. 2022

- Studying at Electrical Computer Engineering Faculty of University of Tehran
- Overall GPA: 3.86 / 4 (18.61 / 20)
- Thesis project: Developing cognitive games for visual/auditory memory improvement of children & elders Supervisor: Prof. Hadi(Manouchehr) Moradi

Certifications

2022	Reinforcement Learning Specialization 🗹	Coursera
2022	Structuring Machine Learning Projects 🗹	Coursera
2021	Core Interaction Programming part of Unity Certified Programmer Exam Preparation Specialization ${f Z}$	Coursera
2021	Neural Networks and Deep Learning 🗷	Coursera
2021	Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter Tuning, Regularization and Optimization $oxize{C}$	Coursera

Honors & Awards

2022	Finalist, for the Best Undergraduate Project Award ピ	University of Tehran
2022	Ranked 11th, out of approximately 105 undergraduate students in Computer Engineering	University of Tehran
2017	Ranked 810th, out of more than 146000 participants in Nationwide Universities Entrance Exam (B.Sc.)	Mashhad, Iran

Soft Skills

Continuous learning Commitment Responsible Hard working Team working Time management

Languages_

English Professional working proficiency **Persian** Native or bilingual proficiency

Portfolio_

Online portfolio with additional details about the projects and my works are available online

SEPEHR RAZMYAR · RÉSUMÉ MAY 31, 2022